{
    "id": "29928ae4bcde49dab3f08140b477ff2e",
    "title": "Gerunds And Infinitives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I hope you don’t mind ……………………….. leaving early.",
            "description": "Gerund is a noun equivalent. It can only be modified by a possessive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0569a26c729e4a10a0882a5ff1fcb5ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are prevented ………………………….. to him.",
            "description": "Prevent is followed by from + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to talk",
                "from talking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "765d40f590984ef683ccd706916e5449"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher encouraged us …………………………… harder.",
            "description": "Encourage is followed by to + infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "to working",
                "working",
                "to work"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5b37860ee1b2473aa731d43c663307f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ………………………….",
            "description": "Tired is followed by of + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to walk",
                "of walking",
                "to walking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c3fced5e4b334a4f8c5706c0c81e3061"
        },
        {
            "question": "We rejoiced at …………………………. winning.",
            "description": "Gerund is a noun equivalent. It can only be modified by a possessive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "his",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3027d7757424c37906dddac18c4ec5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We heard of …………………………. having won another trophy.",
            "description": "Gerund is a noun equivalent. It can only be modified by a possessive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "his",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a14232c0ce984c8abb003b4064f30c55"
        },
        {
            "question": "He insisted on ………………………. being present at the meeting.",
            "description": "Gerund is a noun equivalent. It can only be modified by a possessive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce56ba33d88141ac8fa906cf9537e878"
        },
        {
            "question": "All depends on ………………………… getting the job.",
            "description": "Gerund is a noun equivalent. It can only be modified by a possessive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "his",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3bb794c873324aae9d6a5565047a06e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We left without …………………………. knowing.",
            "description": "Gerund is a noun equivalent. It can only be modified by a possessive expression.",
            "answers": [
                "anyone",
                "anyone's",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0128c187a0449db91e5ead8e6ec8305"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are expected ………………………… work at 8 am every morning.",
            "description": "Expect is followed by an object + infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "starting",
                "to start"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bd536c1a54141419ba0b67ee728c44c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why don’t you let me ………………………..?",
            "description": "Let is followed by object + infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "speaking",
                "to speak",
                "speak"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "143de91b1fa048ba9c5ab2d7c91c9cf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I recommend you ……………………….. this coat.",
            "description": "Recommend can be followed by object + to infinitive or noun clause.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "to buy",
                "buy",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "117e526280c743439fe3e2294585f8c2"
        }
    ]
}